Finding Aid for John and Leni Sinclair Papers 1957-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs
    - Sinclair personal and professional photographs
      - 1978-1999
        - Miscellaneous personal photographs
          - 1970s-1980s (Box 74)
          - 1990s, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Ann Arbor Sun/The Sun
      - Subject file
        - Alcatraz takeover (Box 38)
        - Allende, Mrs. (Box 38)
        - Angola (Box 38)
        - Ann Arbor
          - Art galleries (Box 38)
          - Art Fair 1973 (Box 38)
          - Art World (Box 38)
          - Bars and restaurants (Box 38)
          - City Council (Box 38)
          - Demonstrations 1976 (Box 38)
          - Festival of Life (Box 38)
          - Food Coops (Box 38)
          - Free Clinic (Box 38)
          - Free concerts (Box 38)
            (including Blues and Jazz Festival)
          - Hash Bash (Box 38)
          - Human Rights Party
            - Groups (Box 38)
            - Individuals (Box 38)
          - Localmotion (Box 38)
          - MacDonalds (Box 38)
          - People (Box 38)
          - Peoples' Ballroom (Box 38)
          - Police (Box 38)
          - Postill, Sheriff Fred (Box 38)
          - Rent control (Box 38)
          - Republicans (Box 38)
          - Stevenson, Mayor James (Box 38)
          - Students (Box 38)
          - University of Michigan people (Box 38)
          - Wheeler, Mayor Al (Box 38)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 38)
        - Art (Box 38)
        - Austin, Richard (Box 38)
        - Authors (Box 38)
        - Black Panther Party (Box 38)
        - Bond, Julian (Box 38)
          (with Perry Bullard)
        - Bullard, Perry (Box 38)
        - Busing (Box 38)
        - Cartoons
          - Frayne, Chris (Box 38)
          - Kell, Gary (Box 38)
          - Weinberg, Barbara (Box 38)
        - Chavez, Cesar (Box 38)
        - Children (Box 38)
        - China (Box 38)
        - CIA (Box 38)
        - Cockrel, Ken (Box 38)
        - Conspiracy researchers (Box 38)
          (Mark Lane, et al.)
        - Counter-security (Box 38)
          (Bugs)
        - Davis, Angela (Box 38)
        - Davis, Rennie (Box 38)
        - Democratic Convention 1976 (Box 38)
        - Democrats, Other (Box 38)
        - Demonstrations, National and international (Box 38)
        - Detroit
          - Hospitals (Box 39)
          - Housing (Box 39)
          - Howard Kohn (Box 39)
          - Street gangs (Box 39)
          - Twelfth Precinct trial (Box 39)
          - Wayne County Commission (Box 39)
          - Wayne County Jail (Box 39)
          - WDET (Box 39)
          - Youth Association (Box 39)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 39)
        - Drugs (Box 39)
        - Edwards, George (Box 39)
        - Ellsberg, Daniel (Box 39)
        - Energy crisis (Box 39)
        - Esch, Marvin (Box 39)
        - Feminists' Federal Credit Union and Feminist Women's City Club (Box 39)
        - Film (Box 39)
        - Fletcher, Madeline (Box 39)
        - Fonda, Jane (Box 39)
        - Food (Box 39)
        - Ford, Gerald (Box 39)
        - Gaskin, Stephen (Box 39)
        - Gay liberation (Box 39)
        - Harris, Fred (Box 39)
        - Hayden, Tom (Box 39)
        - Health (Box 39)
        - Highland Park (Box 39)
        - Hoffman, Abbie (Box 39)
        - Housing, Miscellaneous (Box 39)
        - HUD (Box 39)
        - Jackson, Jesse (Box 39)
        - Jamaica (Box 39)
        - Judges (Box 39)
        - Langston Hughes Theater (Box 39)
        - Lawyers (Box 39)
        - Leary, Timothy (Box 39)
        - Michigan politicians (Box 39)
        - Milliken, William (Box 39)
        - Musicians
          - Kooar, Joe (Box 39)
            (photos by)
          - Ledbetter, Dennis (Box 39)
        - NAACP (Box 39)
        - Nader, Ralph (Box 39)
        - Narcotics agents (Box 39)
        - Native Americans (Box 39)
        - Newton, Huey (Box 39)
        - Nixon, Richard (Box 39)
        - Oakland County (Box 39)
        - Oleszko, Pat (Box 39)
        - Ozone parade (Box 39)
        - PBB (Box 39)
        - People, Miscellaneous (Box 39)
        - Pierce, Ed (Box 39)
        - Pontiac Stadium (Box 39)
        - Police, Miscellaneous (Box 39)
        - Prisons (Box 39)
        - PUSH (Box 39)
        - Redlining and urban sprawl (Box 39)
        - Republicans, Miscellaneous (Box 39)
        - Riegle, Don (Box 39)
        - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel (Box 40)
        - Rubin, Jerry (Box 40)
        - Seale, Bobby (Box 40)
        - Schools (Box 40)
        - Simon, Howard (Box 40)
        - Soledad Brothers (Box 40)
        - Sports (Box 40)
        - Sun
          - Colombian contest (Box 40)
          - Iffy the Dopester (Box 40)
          - Staff before 1975/1976 (Box 40)
          - Staff 1975-1976 (Box 40)
          - Logos (Box 40)
        - Swainson, John (Box 40)
        - Teamsters (Box 40)
        - UAW (Box 40)
        - Vets Against War (Box 40)
        - Vietnam (Box 40)
        - Wayne State University (Box 40)
        - Weather people (Box 40)
        - Willow Run Labs (Box 40)
        - Women (Box 40)
        - Young Lords (Box 40)
        - Youth Liberation (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous contact prints and negatives; identified
          - Belle Isle, Hudson's warehouse (Box 40)
          - Black firefighters (Box 40)
          - Madeline Fletcher, 2 sheets (Box 40)
          - Free Press, Pelham (Box 40)
          - B.B. King (Box 40)
          - Joy Lovenmeyers (Box 40)
          - New McKinney Cotton Pickers, Feminist City (Box 40)
          - PCB poisoning, River Rouge (Box 40)
          - La Sandoz? (Box 40)
          - Unemployment, Brenda, The Shadow (Box 40)
          - Virginia Park (Box 40)
          - Nancy Wilson, 3 sheets (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous contact prints and negatives; unidentified, 3 sheets (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous contact prints
          - Ozone parade 10/72 (Box 40)
          - Diesel Smoke (Box 40)
          - Unidentified subjects (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous negatives-Folder 1
          - Baseball (Box 40)
          - Belfast (Box 40)
          - Betty (Box 40)
          - Christmas? (Box 40)
          - Cecil Clarena (Box 40)
          - Derelict (Box 40)
          - Detroit Zoo (Box 40)
          - Dosie? (Box 40)
          - Jim Dulzo, Michael Castleman (Box 40)
          - Eberwhite 2/75 (Box 40)
          - Grain co-op; drug help (Box 40)
          - John Holt (Box 40)
          - Keith Jarrett and Esther Phillips at Hill 2/74 (Box 40)
          - Joy Lovemeyers 6/76 (Box 40)
          - Lynn and Kim Kilo? (Box 40)
          - Parade (Box 40)
          - Personal (Box 40)
          - Radio King Ballroom (Box 40)
          - Stanley and Hobart? (Box 40)
          - Richie Stoneman (Box 40)
          - Joe Tex 6/76 (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous negatives-Folder 2
          - Team for Justice 1973 (Box 40)
          - ABC Conference? (Box 40)
          - Bas relief? (Box 40)
          - Detroit 8/73, 3 sheets (Box 40)
          - Jackie, Barbara (Box 40)
          - Johnny Ferria rally? (Box 40)
          - North Carolina, July 4th rally (Box 40)
          - Wayne County Jail? (Box 40)
        - Miscellaneous negatives-Folder 3
          - Voice of People, abortion rally, St. Joe's (Box 40)
          - Voice of People, aftershots, houses (Box 40)
          - Voice of People, album covers (Box 40)
          - Voice of People, People's Produce Co (Box 40)
          - WCBN, Tavi Fulkerson (Box 40)
          - WDET, 2 sheets (Box 40)
          - Mighty Joe Young, People's Ballroom (Box 40)
          - Unidentified (Box 40)
      - Photographer files
        - "B" and "K" folder
          - B-3, People's Ballroom (Box 41)
          - K-2, Abbie Hoffman in New Haven demonstration 5/70, neg (Box 41)
          - K-4, Unidentified, negative with partial print (Box 41)
          - K-14, Re-elect Nixon sign, police in Chevy incident, "monster digger," 10/72, neg (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 1-10
          - M-1, Work on driveway, S. Viet sister 10/72 (Box 41)
          - M-2, Com. Center 12/72 (Box 41)
          - M-3, New Heavenly Blue album, Bust Bros. radio show 12/72 (Box 41)
          - M-4, Rockets-Crisler 12/09/1972 (Box 41)
          - M-5, Dr. John-Crisler 12/09/1972 (Box 41)
          - M-6, Community Center fire 12/16/1972 (Box 41)
          - M-7, Community Center fire 12/16/1972 (Box 41)
          - M-8, Tribal Council emergency meeting 12/17/1972 (Box 41)
          - M-9, Rockets 01/05/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-10, G.P. at City Council, aftermath of C.C. fire 01/08/1973 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 11/21
          - M-11, Voice of the people, G.P. at City Hall, 1/8 and 9/73 (Box 41)
          - M-11, Sun staff and Community Center group 01/19/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-12, Voice of the people, Masonic Temple 01/20/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-13, Dist. 01/20/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-14, Voice of the people, Masonic Temple 01/20/1973, neg (Box 41)
          - M-15, Luther Allison 2/73, print only (Box 41)
          - M-17, Dave Sinclair 01/26/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-18, Power Center, Mojo Boogie Band 2/73 (Box 41)
          - M-19, Police hearing 2/73 (Box 41)
          - M-20, Mojo Boogie Band 2/73 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 21-30
          - M-21, Rockets 2/73 (Box 41)
          - M-22, Revenue share-T.C. City Council 2/73 (Box 41)
          - M-23, Police demo-David, City Hall 02/12/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-24, 2nd ward candidates at Alice Lloyd 02/14/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-25, RPP open house 02/18/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-26, RPP open house 02/18/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-27, Primary 02/19/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-29, Craig Blazier-arrested 1520 Hill 03/01/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-30, Shop Friday 03/09/1973 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 31-40
          - M-31, Wild Boys at Platt Rd. 03/10/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-32, Pun and Craig-Beulah, Mich., David Fenton 03/19/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-34, Marc and Linda for $ 03/31/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-35, Court hearing for PP and CB, Hash festival 04/01/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-36, Hash festival (State Police) 04/01/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-37, Hash festival 04/01/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-40, Hash festival 04/01/1973 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 41-50
          - M-41, Hash festival 04/01/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-42, Hash festival 04/01/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-42B Hash bash 04/01/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-43, Ransom Boogie-Union, Hash festival 04/01/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-44, Hash festival, Dorm bust hearing 04/01/1973-04/02/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-45, People voting, Republican victory party 04/02/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-46, Dorm bust hearings 04/08/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-47, Uprising in practice room, Republican getting sworn in 04/08/1973-04/09/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-49, Uprising at People's Plaza and 2 pig photos 04/14/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-50, People's Plaza 04/14/1973 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 51-60
          - M-51, People's Plaza 04/14/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-52, Uprising, People's Plaza 04/14/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-53, Alice, Voice of People, Police Robertson 04/27/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-55, Uprising at OCC 05/13/1973 and City Council, 05/21/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-56, Homegrown 05/08/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-57, Joe Harrison, BSF, Art Ensemble, Guitar Army (Box 41)
          - M-58, Linda and Freddie 5/73 (Box 41)
          - M-59, Sun move to 208 First 05/18/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-60, Corner of Main and Huron 05/23/1973 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 61-70
          - M-61, Flack-Full Tilt Boogie, Ballroom 05/12/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-62, Radio King-Odyssey (Box 41)
          - M-63, Radio King-Odyssey (Box 41)
          - M-64, Radio King-Odyssey, print only (Box 41)
          - M-65, City Council, vote on Gay Pride Week, Cy E. Neil L., 2 cops busted PP and CB 06/04/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-66, Gay protests in front of Union, Republicans' house, Pretzel Bell, City Hall 06/05/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-67, Lisa G., A and P, Marks, PP JS conference 06/02/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-68, Lisa and Chris-AFSCME 06/12/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-70, Marijuana public hearing, City Hall 06/09/1973 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 71-80
          - M-71, Marijuana public hearing on $5 law, Marcy 06/09/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-72, Park concert-Uprising, Radio King 06/10/1973, neg (Box 41)
          - M-73, 1st park concert 06/10/1973, neg (Box 41)
          - M-74, First park concert 06/10/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-75, 1st Sunday free park concert 06/10/1973, neg (Box 41)
          - M-77, 1st Sunday concert 06/10/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-79, 2nd park concert, Detroit, food stand 06/17/1973, neg (Box 41)
          - M-80, 2nd park concert, Detroit, Lightnin', CJQ 06/17/1973, neg (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 81-90
          - M-81, Poetry festival, Di Prima 06/19/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-82, Eden food stand 06/19/1973, neg (Box 41)
          - M-83, Food co-op pick-up at Northside School 06/23/1973, neg (Box 41)
          - M-84, Detroit Eastern Market 06/23/1973, neg (Box 41)
          - M-85, Third Sunday concert 06/24/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-86, Republicans-City Hall 06/25/1973 (Box 41)
          - M-88, Narcs (Clarence Rye, unidentified), Gay Pride Week 7/73, neg (Box 41)
          - M-90, John from the Odyssey 06/02/1973 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 91-120
          - M-91, Lansing Pun and Craig news conference, neg (Box 41)
          - M-95A Art Fair, B and J billboard, Summer 73 (Box 41)
          - M-96, Brooklyn Blues Busters at Milan, Summer 73 (Box 41)
          - M-112, Free med. clinic 10/73 (Box 41)
          - M-113, Free medical clinic 10/73 (Box 41)
          - M-114, Impeach Nixon demonstration 10/73 (Box 41)
          - M-115, Uprising, Spring 1973 (Box 41)
          - M-116, Uprising, Spring 1973 (Box 41)
          - M-117, Uprising, Spring 1973 (Box 41)
          - M-118, Ozone parade, Nica and Terry at Burns Park 10/73 (Box 41)
          - M-119, Riot, Dallas, Bar shots 10/73 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 121-140
          - M-127, Dylan line, Hill Hall, Carson-gas, neg (Box 41)
          - M-131, Demonstration at Purple Pickle 1/74, neg (Box 41)
          - M-132, Lee Gill, HRP filing petitions 9/73, neg (Box 41)
          - M-134, Blind Pig Record Co., Tommy, Jerry, Milt 2/74, neg (Box 41)
          - M-135, MacDonald's demonstration 2/74, neg (Box 41)
          - M-137, Hunter Thompson 02/12/1974 (Box 41)
          - M-138, 3rd World Solidarity Conference, Angela Davis 3/74 (Box 41)
          - M-139, 3rd World Solidarity Conference, Clyde Belle 3/74 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 141-150
          - M-141, Esther Phillips, Charlie Haden, Gato Barbieri, Keith Jarret 3/74 (Box 41)
          - M-142, Temptations, Tower of Power 4/74 (Box 41)
          - M-143, Festival of Life 4/74 (Box 41)
          - M-144, Hash Bash 04/01/1974 (Box 41)
          - M-148, International Women's Day celebration 3/74, neg (Box 41)
          - M-149, Allen Ginsberg 4/74, neg (Box 41)
          - M-150, Wasson-Postill hearing 5/74 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 151-160
          - M-151, Preparing Otis Spann site for park concerts 5/74 (Box 41)
          - M-151A 1st park concert 5/74 (Box 41)
          - M-152, Commander Cody 5/74, neg (Box 41)
          - M-154, Blind Pig friends road show 5/74 (Box 41)
          - M-155, Gay Pride vs. city Repubs., Zenta Dance 6/74 (Box 41)
          - M-156, V.O.P. 6/74 (Box 41)
          - M-157, 1st park concert 5/74 (Box 41)
          - M-160, 1st $5 weed ticket, U of M striker, cops 7/74 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 161-210
          - M-161, Soulful Soulmates 6/74 (Box 41)
          - M-163, Tim Leary circa 1972, print only (Box 41)
          - M-164, Richard Pryor, Hill 9/74, print only (Box 41)
          - M-164A Taj Mahal 10/74, print only (Box 41)
          - M-171, HRP and Democratic county commissioners, neg (Box 41)
          - M-180, City Council Creeps (Republicans) 9/74, neg (Box 41)
          - M-197, Hash Bash 04/01/1975 (Box 41)
          - M-201, Crater fill 5/75 (Box 41)
          - M-203, Wheeler swearing in 5/75 (Box 41)
          - M-204, Fred Harris 6/75, print only (Box 41)
          - M-206, Westside benefit for School of Creative Music, free concert, Native American sit-in at Fleming 6/75 (Box 41)
        - "M" folder, nos. 211-230
          - M-215, Chances Are ladies night 7/75 (Box 41)
          - M-216, Sound service, Warshal 7/75 (Box 41)
          - M-221, Ann Arbor Art Fair 7/75 (Box 41)
          - M-222, Ann Arbor Art Fair 7/75, neg (Box 41)
          - M-223, Ann Arbor Art Fair 7/75, neg (Box 41)
          - M-224, Ann Arbor Art Fair 7/75 (Box 41)
          - M-225, Brooks Patterson 9/75 (Box 41)
        - "M" subsubseries of contact sheets, 19 envelopes (Box 41)
        - "X" folder
          - X-1, Doctor John 06/04/1972 (Box 41)
          - X-2, Doctor John and Quicksilver 06/04/1972 (Box 41)
          - X-3, Doctor John and Quicksilver 06/04/1972 (Box 41)
          - X-4, Ann Arbor, Heavenly Blue, Otis Spann Park 06/08/1972 (Box 41)
          - X-5, Detroit People's Ballroom, Free concert O.C.C. 06/25/1972 (Box 41)
          - X-6, WRIF freebie, F. Bach 07/11/1972 (Box 41)
          - X-7, Radio King, Iris Bell 08/30/1972 (Box 41)
        - Eckert, Bob
          - Auto plant, unidentified, 4 sheets prints only (Box 42)
          - Renaissance Center 7/76 (Box 42)
          - Feminist Women's City Club, Sun staff 9/76 (Box 42)
          - Police 9/76 (Box 42)
        - GKG
          - Police, G.G. 1st precinct 09/05/1976, 2 sheets (Box 42)
          - Police, G.G. 5th precinct 9/76, 2 sheets (Box 42)
          - Carlton Elementary School 09/09/1976 (Box 42)
          - Kettering High School 09/09/1976, 2 sheets (Box 42)
        - Johnson, David--folder 1
          - Detroit General Hospital 03/20/1976 (Box 42)
          - Brecker Brothers at Masonic 4/76 (Box 42)
          - Fantastic Four, Special Delivery, Quickest Way out, Chuck Jackson 4/76 (Box 42)
          - Roberta Flack 4/76 (Box 42)
          - Billy Holcomb Support Comm. 4/76 (Box 42)
          - Nadine Brown 4/76 (Box 42)
          - Teddy Pendergrass 4/76, 2 sheets (Box 42)
          - UAW convention 4/76 (Box 42)
          - Grover Washington, Jr., at Masonic 4/76 (Box 42)
          - Detroit Tigers opening game 04/14/1976, 3 sheets (Box 42)
          - Rod Rodgers rehearsal 04/27/1976 (Box 42)
          - Rod Rodgers Dance Company 04/29/1976, 2 sheets (Box 42)
        - Johnson, David--folder 2 May-June, 1976
          - Abandoned buildings (Box 42)
          - Abandoned houses (Box 42)
          - Advertisers (Box 42)
          - Belle Isle (Box 42)
          - Abandoned houses and buildings (Box 42)
          - Banks and banking compositions (Box 42)
          - Stanley Black (Box 42)
          - Detroit Tigers-The Bird (Box 42)
          - Sound Suite, neg (Box 42)
          - Sound Suite, Motown Record studio, neg (Box 42)
          - Four Tops, Roostertail, 3 sheets (Box 42)
          - J.L. Hudson's flag (Box 42)
          - J.L. Hudson's flag, Sun move (Box 42)
          - Eddie Kendricks (Box 42)
        - Johnson, David--folder 3
          - Kenny Burrell 7/76, 3 sheets (Box 42)
          - Sun picnic 7/76 (Box 42)
          - Grady Tate, Eddie Jefferson 7/76 (Box 42)
          - Basketball game Sun/WJZZ undated, 3 sheets (Box 42)
          - The Bird undated (Box 42)
          - Fire and boy on bus undated (Box 42)
          - Open house undated, 2 sheets (Box 42)
          - Wayne County Jail, Hudson's Warehouse, 1200 Beaubien undated (Box 42)
        - Johnson, David--folder 4
          - Unidentified, 2 sheets (Box 42)
        - Marks, Michael
          - Rock concerts, including Edgar Winter and Average White Band undated, 7 sheets prints only (Box 42)
        - Ross, Linda--folder 1
          - Crater arrests 06/17/1972 (Box 42)
          - Craters 07/04/1972, 2 sheets (Box 42)
          - Free concert, 8th Day 07/09/1972, 3 sheets (Box 42)
          - Cable Commission meeting 07/12/1972 (Box 42)
          - Sunday funnies 07/16/1972 (Box 42)
          - Free concert, Tribal Council, food 06/16/1972 (Box 42)
          - Commander Cody, Earth shoes 07/31/1972 (Box 42)
        - Ross, Linda--folder 2
          - Guardian Angel, park, Art Ensemble 08/13/1972 (Box 42)
          - Pigs at park, Radio King 08/20/1972 (Box 42)
          - Kid and Radio King, park 08/20/1972 (Box 42)
          - Sarah Brown 08/20/1972 (Box 42)
          - Work on houses, DS on Cable Commission 10/72 (Box 42)
          - Ozone parade 10/72 (Box 42)
          - Dry walling hall, St. Joes, painting Community Center 11/72 (Box 42)
          - Rangers, Voice of People 12/09/1972 (Box 42)
          - Video, Crisler 12/09/1972 (Box 42)
          - Rio Smokehouse 11/20/1973 Mojo Boogie, Ballroom, 11/26/1973 (Box 42)
        - Ross, Linda--folder 3
          - Art Ensemble, Dedication ceremony, Lucille Spann, Koko Taylor, Mighty Joe Young, Willy Dixon and Boogie Woogie Red (Box 42)
          - Marion Brown, Boogie Bros., Jane Fonda (Box 42)
          - Commander Cody's Airmen (Box 42)
          - Miles Davis, Boogie Bros (Box 42)
          - Diag with police and crowds, slides (Box 42)
          - Digging (Box 42)
            print only
          - Dr. John, Pharoah Sanders (Box 42)
          - Double wildness (Box 42)
          - Grand Funk at Cobo October (Box 42)
          - Park, Voice of People (Box 42)
          - People's Ballroom (Box 42)
          - Police bus (Box 42)
          - Pun and Craig news conference, Lansing (Box 42)
          - Rockets (Box 42)
          - Sinclair news conference (Box 42)
          - Union Ballroom, Voice of People, Hawj ?, Scott Morgan (Box 42)
          - Up and Wild Boys at park, WNRZ at park (Box 42)
          - Voting (Box 42)
          - Unidentified (Box 42)
        - Ross, Linda--folder 4
          - Luther Allison, Mojo Boogie Band, Anne Lavasseur, Genie P., crowd shots, Bonnie Raitt, Sippie Wallace, Mighty Joe Young, Archie Shepp (Box 42)
          - Boogie Woogie Red, Voice of People (Box 42)
          - Commander Cody and His Lost Planet Airmen at Hill (Box 42)
          - Craters 1972 (Box 42)
          - Sun Ra, Howlin' Wolf (Box 42)
          - Voice of People, free clinic, voting (Box 42)
          - Muddy Waters and sidemen, crowd faces (Box 42)
        - Unangst, Joel
          - Joyce Garrett, Ann Besor 11/75 (Box 42)
          - Martha Jean 6/76 (Box 42)
          - Frank Kelley 8/76 (Box 42)
          - Harlem Square Gallery 9/76 (Box 42)
        - Weinberg, Barbara
          - Ken Cockrel, Al Wheeler, Bruce Springsteen, Fred Harris 1975 (Box 42)
          - Bob Seger 1975 (Box 42)
          - Abandoned buildings 2/76 (Box 42)
          - Senator Hart 3/76 (Box 42)
          - Dick "Night Train" Lane 3/76 (Box 42)
          - Highland Park 8/76, 2 sheets (Box 42)
          - Stanley Turrentine, Don Riegle 9/76 (Box 42)
        - Wiatrak, Ken
          - Unidentified, 2 sheets print only (Box 42)
        - Miscellaneous photographers; negatives only
          - Boyd, Melba
            - Billy Holcomb 7/74 (Box 42)
            - Olympics 7/76 (Box 42)
          - Fenton, David
            - Coleman Young (Box 42)
          - Fort, Derryk
            - Alex Pollich (Box 42)
            - Unidentified (Box 42)
          - Grambau, Hugh
            - State capitol building 5/76 (Box 42)
          - Keife, Tim
            - John Otterbacher, Dennis Cawthorne, state capitol (Box 42)
          - Knapp, Dave (print only)
            - Hash Bash 1974 (Box 42)
          - Lamb, Ed
            - Jerry Butler at Lowmans 2/76 (Box 42)
            - Johnny Taylor 2/76 (Box 42)
          - Prazzato, Jan